webcasterwp.com 2017-02-07

# Privacy Policy | WebCasterWP

The following describes the Privacy Policy for our website.

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us.  To better protect your privacy we  
provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the  
choices you can make about the way your information is collected and  
used.  You agree to agree to these policies by virtue of using our  
website in a way that leads to you providing us with personal  
information.

**State Law & Accompanying Rights**  
Please understand that you may have additional rights originating from State  
laws based on where you live.  These State-based rights may  
augment, strengthen, or otherwise somehow compliment any privacy rights  
you have inherently or under Federal law.  Our policy is to comply  
fully with the privacy policies of every jurisdiction in which we  
operate.  Accordingly, you are free to use our Contact information  
to reach us at any time to assert any State rights.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**  
Protecting  
the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason,  
our website will never collect or maintain information at our website  
from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is  
structured to attract anyone under 18.

Under our Terms of Service and Conditions of Use, children under 18 are not  
allowed to use our website and access our services.  It is not our  
intention to offer products or services to minors.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting our website, the IP address used to access our website may be  
logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is  
purely used to analyze trends, administer our website, track users  
movement, and gather broad demographic information for internal use  
such as statistical assessments and website improvement. Most  
importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally  
identifiable information.

Other information may be collected as well, which is rather typical of most  
websites.  For instance, the source that referred you to our  
website is generally known.  Likewise, your duration on our  
website, and your destination when you leave our website can also be  
tracked.  Other common data collected includes the type of  
operating system the computer you are using to access our website  
has.  Similarly, the type of web browser is often noted.  
Again, this is common data collection, and helps ultimately produce a  
better end-user experience.

Cookies are another common internet practice.  Cookies are a key means of  
improving user experience by allows us to customize your use of our  
website.  Simple information is transferred to your computer to  
allow the content and experience to reflect your actions, preferences,  
and so on.  You should simply make the assumption our website uses  
cookies, and note that you are free to make adjustments in your web  
browser to disable these or otherwise receive notification of cookies  
so you can take whatever desired action you so choose.  Please  
understand that refusing cookies may cripple some of our website  
features and render some aspects useless to you.

At times, you will be fully aware of information received, as you are the  
direct source providing it.  For instance, you may comment on a  
blog post, reply to an email (whether broadcast message or  
autoresponder), provide an email address, complete a survey, requests  
SMS, or otherwise.  Likewise, purchases necessarily involve  
collecting certain information, such as credit card information, PayPal  
addresses, your physical address for billing and/or shipping, phone  
number, and so on.  Refusing to provide some of this information  
may lead to us being unable to provide you with the products or  
services you’ve requested.

A prime example of limited access to our website is where content may be  
protected by a username and password.  Whether a username and  
password is generated by our website, or created by you, these will  
almost always be connected with some other information related to or  
connected with you.  This is true since much content that is  
protected on the internet is subscription based, often paid for.  
Thus, the username and password must necessarily be tied to your other  
account data.  Usernames and passwords, by their very nature,  
should be kept private.

**Handling of Personal Information**  
Note that any personal information you provide to others apart from us or  
our vendors is wholly optional.  As an example, you might disclose  
something in a blog post comment.  That “private” information is  
now “public,” and we have no control over that.  In like fashion,  
you sharing information with any other third party not functioning as a  
service provider to us puts that information beyond our control and  
becomes subject to the policy that party has in place.

Our primary intention for collecting personal and private information from  
you is simply to conduct our business.  We can use this internally  
to better serve you.  Accordingly, we see no reason to share your  
personal information to other parties and outside interests unless you  
have authorized us to do so.  Of course, there are instances where  
your information is stored with third party service providers, such as  
email service providers, as they provide services that are  
industry-leading in quality and security and are far more beneficial to  
our end user than attempting such services “in-house.”  However,  
you are never required to deal with any such third party directly, they  
are limited in how they use your information, and they cannot sell or  
transfer it to others in any way.

However,  
of course, your information does comprise part of an overall  
whole.  This aggregate of information, by contrast, may be used to  
understand our overall user base.  Further, we may share this  
information about our website visitors as a whole, not individually,  
with third parties for various purposes, in our sole discretion.

While  
we are staunch privacy advocates, there are times when even we may be  
forced to abandon these ideals.  Just as major search engines face  
ongoing compulsion to provide data against their will, so too may the  
same occur with our website.  Illegal activity or other serious  
acts or allegations could create legal liability for our website.  
In those cases, we reserve the right to share your information, or else  
may simply be compelled to do so by law.  On the other hand, there  
may be times when we would need to share your private information in  
order to protect our own interests.  For instance, in cases of  
suspected or alleged copyright infringement or other intellectual  
property violations, it may be necessary to share personal information.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google,  
as a third party advertisement vendor, may use cookies to serve ads on  
this website. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve  
adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website,  
including past visits, as well as other websites on the internet.

To  
opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content  
network privacy policy at the following url  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the  
DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other  
Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track  
users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness  
and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies,  
our website has no access or control over these cookies that may be  
used by third party advertisers.  However, you can opt out of  
some, though likely not all, of these cookies in one easy location at  
http://ww.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
We  
have included links on this website for your use and reference. We are  
not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should  
be aware that the privacy policies of these websites may differ from  
our own.

**CHANGE NOTICE:**  As  
with any of our administrative and legal notice pages, the contents of  
this page can and will change over time.  Accordingly, this page  
could read differently as of your very next visit.  These changes  
are necessitated, and carried out, in order to protect you and our  
website.  If this page is important to you, you should check back  
frequently as no other notice of changed content will be provided  
either before or after the change takes effect.

**COPYRIGHT WARNING:**

The legal notices and administrative pages on this website, including this  
one, have been diligently drafted by an attorney.  We have paid to  
license the use of these legal notices and administrative pages for  
your protection and ours.  This material may not be used in any  
way for any reason and unauthorized use is policed via Copyscape to  
detect violators.

**QUESTIONS/COMMENTS/CONCERNS:**

****  If you have any questions about the contents of this page, or simply wish  
to reach us for any other reason, you may do so by using our [Contact information.](http://webcasterwp.com/support)
